Finding Aid for the The Nelson and Marion Fuson Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Nelson and Marion Fuson Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0161
1.68 linear_feet
- Correspondence - Outgoing, April 1949 - January 1970
  - Professor E.R. Pinkson, U.S. Naval Academy
  - Dr. R. T. Abercrombie, Johns Hopkins Club
  - Mr. Barbour
  - Ralph and Marian Harlow
  - Dennis Hudson and Barbara Johnson
  - Rev. Kelly Miller Smith
  - Mrs. H. C. Darnell and Rev. and Mrs. C. G. Fuson
  - Dr. Madison Sarratt, Mayor's Committee on Human Relations
  - Dr. and Mrs. Looby
  - Rev. James Bevel, Student Non-Violent Movement
  - Pegg
  - Chancellor Harrie Branscomb, Vanderbilt University
  - E. Mack Cates
  - H. C. Nottebart
  - R. L. Prescott
  - John Sloan
  - C. H. Handley
  - Fred Harvey, Jr.
  - Joe Zahalka
  - Norbert W. Smith, Bus Caravan from Detroit
  - Katherine Jones
  - Dan Fuson to Catherine in jail
  - Allan Fuson to Pauline in jail
  - Matthew Walker, Jr.
  - John and Bernard
  - Students in jail
  - Governor Ellington with Petition for Reinstatment of Students at TN A & I State U.
  - Bernard Lafayette, Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee
  - Mr. Zimmerman
  - National Conference of Friends on Race Relations
  - Avon Williams
- Correspondence - Incoming, October 1946 - June 1974
  - Gloria Washington
  - Miriam B. Ryan
  - Earl R. Pinkson
  - Nicholas Hobbs, Peabody College
  - Sue and Dave Minter and Lindsey and Gene Cox
  - Glenn E. Smiley
  - Lindsey Cox
  - Ralph Harlow
  - Roger Shinn (Attached to Letter to Ralph Harlow)
  - Dennis Hudson
  - Kelly Miller Smith, NCLC
  - David N. Wiley
  - Columbia Broadcasting System
  - Diane Nash and Peggy Alexander
  - Marilyn Johnson
  - Dr. J. Robert Nelson
  - Dolores Crump
  - Diane Nash
  - T.L. Shuttlesworth
  - Dick Shroeder
  - Pauline to Allan Fuson
  - catherine Burks to Danny Fuson
  - Glen otis Martin
  - Roy Williams of Wilson Quick
  - cornell Hewson
  - Bill Chambless
  - Martha Ragland
  - susan Wilsthire
  - Susan Wiltshire
  - Martha Ragland
  - Mrs. Jessie Carney Smith
  - A. D. Gill, Gulf Oil Corporation with Article "The Changing Face of Gulf in Nigeria
- General Correspondence
  - Letter to Ralph Harlow from Roger L. Shinn
  - Letter to Friends from Dorie Ladner
  - Letter to Mr. T. M. King from I. E. Otey
  - Letter to Avon Williams from Mrs. Le o Burson
- Writings by Nelson Fuson
  - Bill to Reorganize the Local Courts
  - Letter to the Editor The Tennessean
  - Note: Malcolm X Record Club
  - Note: student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee
  - Notes on panel discussion on Non- Violence
  - List of Recommended Books on Negros
- Personal Notes
  - Addresses
  - Letters-handwritten
  - Work Projects list
  - Selma to Montgomery March
- Writings by Others - Martha Ragland
  - Newsletter of the Tennessee Council on Human Relations
  - Letter to the Editor
  - Letter to Mayor Beverly Briley
  - "Motivations and Methods of White Power"
  - Letter to Robert c. Weaver, Sect. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development
  - "The Democratic Party in Tennessee"
- Writings by Others - Edwin Mitchell
  - Lecture No. 7 "New Directions in Human Relations"
  - Sermon delivered at Lenten Service of Christ Church Episcopal
  - Letter to Alexander Looby Notes taken on speech delivered by Robert Bonthius
  - Letter to William Mason
- Political Career - Avon Williams
  - Political Advertisement
  - Newspaper clipping, "State Senate District 19"
  - Questionnaire for Candidates to Tennessee General Assembly
  - Notes of Meeting to Honor Atty. Avon Williams
- Academic Career - Howard and Fisk Universities
  - Newsletter of the Social Order Committees of the Philadelphia Yearly Meetings of the Society of Friends
  - Letter to Clerks of Monthly Meetings from J. Harold Passmore
  - Sigma Xi Club Lecture, Howard University
  - Report of the President's Committee on Civil Rights
  - Brotherhood Pledge campaign
  - Speaker Outline: "The Double standard" NAACP
  - Notice of Mass Meeting of NAACP with program including Kelly Miller Smith
  - Letter to Friends from Nancy and Jim st. John
  - Letter to Guy Taylor from Ned Bollinger of General Board of Education, Methodist Church
  - Letter to Albert Wertham from Ned Bollinger
  - Letter to James c. Barbour from Ned Bollinger
  - Letter to James c. Barbour from Ingram Bloch
  - Letter to Colleague from Fisk Campus Committee, NAACP
  - Letter from Robert Rempfer for United Negro College Fund
  - Letter from Pastor of Gordon Methodist Church to Friends with petition regarding Negro Youth in Nashville Youth Symphony Orchestra
- Events - 1Oth Annual Race Relations Institute - Fisk University
  - Program about Thurgood Marshall
  - Selected Bibliography
  - Selected Pamphlets and Periodicals
  - Speech Delivered by Charles S. Johnson "The Future is Here"
- Events - Lawson Case - Vanderbilt University
  - Letter from Lorrain Giddings to Fusons
  - Statement from the General Cabinet of the Student Christian Association
  - The Lawson-Vanderbilt Affair: Letters to Dean Nelson
- Events - Work Camp Eigtheenth Avenue Community Center
  - Schedule
  - List: Outdoor Improvement Needs for Nursery School
  - List of participants
  - Menus, grocery list
  - List of Work Camp Possibilities
  - Letter promoting the Work Camp
  - "It Can Happen Here" Summary of Work Camp experience
- Events - Fisk Institute
  - Names and addresses of participants in Ultraviolet-Visible Session
  - Names and addresses of participants in the GLC Institute
- Events - 26th Annual Race Relations Institute - Fisk University
  - Handwritten notes
  - List: United Church Board for Homeland Ministries
  - Address: "Black Separatism and Race Relations: Implications and Prospects" by Herman H. Long
  - Address: Robert L. Terrell, Morehouse College
  - Signatures of attendees
  - Draft for outline
  - Notes
  - Program Schedule
- Events - Martin Luther King Holiday Celebration
  - "Join the King March" Program, Legislastive Plaza, 1/19/87 Notice:
- Events - Planning Information for Student Leadership Conference and 30th Anniversary Sit-in Reunion
  - Minutes of meeting
  - Minutes of meeting
  - Agenda of meeting
  - Minutes of Workshop Committee
  - Minutes of Planning Committee
  - Minutes of Planning Committee
  - Handwritten notes; minutes
  - Press Release
- Events - Student Leadership Confererence and 30th Anniversitv Sit-in Reunion
  - Thirty Years Registration Certificates of Appreciation to Marian and Nelson Fuson
  - Agenda of meeting
  - Agenda of meeting
  - Agenda of meeting
  - Schedule, 2/22-24/90
- Organizations and Community Activities - Community Conference on Employment Opportunity (CCEO)
  - Mailing List, 3/60-10/60
  - Letter to Fusons from Wallace T. Dooley and Kelly Miller Smith, with Resolution in Support of the Conference
  - Origin of the Conference
  - Elected Officers
  - Report: "Employment Opportunity for Nashville Negroes" by Vivian W. Henderson
  - Minutes of General Meeting
  - Agenda
  - Minutes of Executive Committee
  - Prospectus for 1961 Conference on Equal Employment Opportunity
- Organizations and Community Activities - CCEO General Correspondence
  - CCEO Meeting Reminder
  - NAACP Letter to Lyndon B. Johnson
  - Letter to Nashville Surgical Supply Company from N. Fuson with response from Roy Williams of Wilson Quick
  - Program: "A Human Relations Audit" sponsored by the Social Action Committee
  - Report on CCEO by N. Fuson
  - Minutes
  - Handwritten Notes
  - Listing of Possible Projects and Targets for Action
- Organizations and Community Activities - CCEO Commission on Industrial Firms
  - List of Names, addresses, telephone numbers
  - Planning Meeting
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Letter from Eli Cohen, National Committee on Employment of Youth
  - Letter to N. Fuson from Wallace T. Dooley
  - Letter to N. Fuson from Wallace T. Dooley
  - Gentle Reminder
  - Registration form
  - Report of Visitation Committee
  - Letter from Commission to Henry Ford
  - Letter from N. Fuson to Byron L. Clark of AVCO
  - General handwritten notes
  - Memos
  - Letter from Doris P. Dennison to Myron B. Towns
  - Letter to F. Donald Hart from N. Fuson
  - Memo to subcommittee visiting Genesco
  - Report of subcommittee on Industrial Firms: DuPont Company Summary of Preliminary Meetings of the CCEO Commission on Industrial Firms
  - Handwritten interview with Ford Motor Company Glass Plant
  - Progress Report on Negro Employment Opportunity in Nashville with Recommendations
  - Typed interview with Western Electric
  - Memo Re: the AVCO Situation
  - Memo to N. Fuson from Gideon Fryer, NCRC
  - Memo Re: Phone call to B. L. Clark, AVCO
  - Memo to Tarleton, Miller and Elliott Re: Conference with Williams of Wilson Quick
  - Letter to Wallace T. Dooley, Meharry from Sherman N.Webster, Social Action Committee
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Christian Leadership Council (NCLC) - Executive Committee
  - List of NCLC Officers
  - Minutes of Executive Committtee
  - Letter to Bert Bigelow from Fusons with Response 9/61 Minutes of Meeting
  - Letter to N. Fuson from Kelly Miller Smith 11/63 Letter to N. Fuson from Andrew White
- Organizations and Community Activtities - Nashville Christian Leadership Council (NCLC) - Budget and Financial Campaign
  - Flyer: "Without Your Help Our Hands are Chained"
  - "Toward the Beloved Community: Story of the NCLC"
  - General Agreements with NAACP
  - Minutes of Meeting
  - Letter to Fusons from Matthew Walker
  - General Letter from N. Fuson
  - Letter to N. Fuson from Kelly Miller Smith
  - Newsletter: Support Operation Open City
  - Letter to Fusons from Bernard Lafayette
  - Paper: "This is NCLC"
  - Letter to James E. Parkin from Nelson Fuson
  - Letter to N. Fuson from H.E. Braden and Andrew White
  - Minutes Financial Campaign Meeting
  - Project Committee Progress Report
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Christian Leadership Council (NCLC) - Financial Reports
  - Summary Financial Statement
  - Summary Financial Statement
  - Summary Financial Statement
  - Summary Financial Statement
  - Summary Financial Statement
  - Letter to Friend from Kelly Miller Smith
  - Letter to whom it may concern from Matthew Walker
  - Financial Satements, January - April 1963
  - Budgeted Expenditures, 10/63-9/64
- Organizations and Community Activities-Nashville Christian Leadership Council (NCLC) - General Correspondence
  - Letter from Student Non-Violent Movement Central Committee
  - Letter to Citizens of Nashville from Nashville Student Non- Violent Movement
  - Petition for Reinstatement of Students at Tennesee A & I
  - Letter to Salynn McCollum from N. Fuson
  - Suggested draft of NCLC letter to Salynn McCollum
  - Letter to NCLC Financial Aid Committee from Salynn McCollum
  - Letter to Financial Aid Committee from Salynn McCollum
  - Letter from Mrs. W. C. McCollum to N. Fuson
  - Letter to Mrs. McCollum
  - Tentative draft of policy statement of the Financial Aid Committee of NCLC
  - Mass Meeting Notice
  - Tentative form NCLC Financial Aid Committee
  - Draft Letter Financial Aid Committee
  - Letter to Mrs. W.C. McCollum from Kelly Miller Smith
  - Letter to Salynn McCollum from Kelly Miller Smith
  - Letter to Wyatt Waller, SCLC from N. Fuson, NCLC Financial Aid Committee
  - Letter to Wyatt Walker from N. Fuson
  - Letter to Wyatt Walker from N. Fuson Notes: Fiancial Aid Committee
  - Draft memo for Financial Campaign
  - Letter to Campaign Committe Members form Inman Otey
  - Petition to Mayor Beverly Briley
  - Minutes of Meeting: Financial Campaign Notice: NCLC Fight for Freedom Bowling Program
  - Letter to Mrs. Fuson from Inman Otey
  - Letter to Friend of Freedom from Kelly Miller Smith
  - Letter to Citizens of the Nashville Community from Kelly Miller Smith and Andrew White
  - Letter from Inman Otey to Friend of Freedom
  - Letter Re: March to Washington
  - from Kelly Miller Smith
  - Notice: Freedom Rally Day, Washington, D.C.
  - Letter to Fellow Student from Ron K. Parker, Grad Student, Vanderbilt University
  - Paper: "Toward the Beloved Community: Story of the NCLC"
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Christian Leadership Council (NCLC) - General Information
  - Structure of the Nashville Christian Leadership Council
  - Letter to N. Fuson from Kelly Miller Smith and Andrew White
  - Newsletter: "News and Notes on National Operation Freedom"
  - Letter to N. Fuson from Roy J. Williams of Wilson Quick
  - Ad: "H.G. Hill: If you Hire, We will Buy"
  - Letter to Co-Worker from Matthew Walker, Chair of Financial Campaign
  - Letter from Kelly Miller Smith to Friend
  - Minutes of Meetings
  - Letter from N. Fuson to Matthew Walker
  - Letter to Matthew Walker from N. Fuson
  - Letter to Matthew Walker from N. Fuson
  - Memo to Matthew Walker from N. Fuson
  - Letter from Matthew Walker Re: financial campaign
  - Program: Operation Open City presents Martin Luther King, Jr. speaking for Civil Rights and Human Dignity
  - Letter to Barry Eseher from Kelly Miller Smith
  - Letter to Rachel Baker from Kelly Miller Smith 1962 Suggested NCLC Campaign Committee 1962 List of Typical Expenditures
  - Ad: "Without Your Help Our Hands are Chained"
  - Tentative Draft of letter with rewrite
  - Financial Campagin Committee Meeting Financial Campaign Committee
  - Letter from J.E. Lowery, Interdenominational Ministers Committee, with copy of Voice of the Movement 2/2 8/62
  - Letter to Campaign Members from Matthew Walker Steering Finance Committee
  - Letter to Burton and Sue from N. Fuson
  - Letter to Friends of Freedom from Inman Otey and Kelly Miller Smith
  - Names added to 1962 mail appeal list for NCLC Financial campaign
  - Letter to James E. Parkin from N. Fuson with Response
  - Letter to James V. Davis, Mayor of Albany, Georgia from N. Fuson
  - Handwritten notes re: Avon Williams and Daniel Williams Copy of Diary of 16 year old girl in jail
  - 5/64 Notice of Assembly for NAACP
  - Letter for support of Poor People's Campaign, Martin Luther King's March on Washington
  - Memo/Newsletter to Contributors from SCLC Staff
  - Notes/Minutes on Meeting
- Organizations and Community Activities - NCLC - Mass Meetings
  - Mass Meeting Program-Seay-Hubbard Methodist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Payne Chapel A.M.E. Church
  - Nashville 1960: Its Problems and Possibilities: Two-Evening Meeting
  - Notice: Martin Luther King to speak 4/20/60 6/60 Mass Meeting Program-Corinthian Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-15th Avenue Church of Christ
  - Mass Meeting Agenda
  - Mass Meeting Program-Kayne Avenue Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Clark Memorial Methodist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Ebenezer Missionary Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-J. Metz Rollins, Presiding
  - Mass Meeting Program-C.T. Vivian, Presiding
  - Letter to Friend from Kelly Miller Smith
  - Mass Meeting Program-Kayne Avenue Baptist Church
  - 6/61 Mass Meeting Program-First Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-First Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Sylvan Steet Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-James Lawson, Presiding
  - Mass Meeting Program-15th Avenue Church of Christ
  - Mass Meeting Program-Clark Memorial Methodist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Roger Heights Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Clark Memorial Methodist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Kayne Avenue Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Mt. Olive Baptist Church
  - Regular Meeting Announcement-Clark Memorial Methodist Church and Mass Meeting Announcement-Gay-Lea Christian Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Gay Lea Christian Church
  - Notice: Regular Meeting-Clark Memorial Methodist Church and Mass Meeting-Mt. Olive Baptist Church
  - Mass Meeting Program-Mt. Zion Primitive Baptist Church
- Organizations and Community Activties - NCLC - Sit-In Papers
  - Purposes and Principles of the NCLC
  - Chronological Summary of Nashville Sit-In Demonstration
  - Notes of Telephone Call to Dennis Hudson
  - Notes of People to Call Suggesting they Attend NCLC Mass Meeting
  - Notes of People to Call to form nucleus of the Committee of 100 Agenda
  - Nelson Fuson talk at Current Events Luncheon Wesley Foundation concerning Fisk, A & I, Vanderbilt Student Sit-ins
  - Letter to Friends from NCLC Citizens Liaison Committee
  - Letter to Silvia Saunders from N. Fuson acknowledging receipt of contribution
  - Calendar of events
  - "Nashville Sit-in Situation" Marion and Nelson Fuson Talk to Bill Fuson's Sociology Class
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Community Relations Council (NCRC) - General Information
  - Community Workshop program
  - Summary of the Findings of Twelve Workshop Discusssion Groups
  - Workshop Notes
  - Summary Report of Nashville's First Workshop on "The Supreme Court Decision and its Meaning for Our Community"
  - Letter to Nelson and Marian from Gene
  - Duke Student Paper: "School's Segregation Policy is 'Barbaric'" 1956 Invitation to become a Charter Member of NCRC
  - Community Workshop Group Assignments: "School Integration: How and When?"
  - Community Workshop program
  - Notes taken at workshop
  - Memo to Charter Members
  - Memorial to Mrs. Johnson
  - Discussion Groups
  - Report of Nashville 1961: Human Relations Inventory
  - Constitution of NCRC
  - Memo Re: Study Meeting 3/30-31
  - Report of Meeting: "Six Years of Public Desegregation in Nashville and Davidson County"
  - List of Officers: Executive Committee and Board of Directors
  - Minutes of Executive Committee
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Community Relations Council (NCRC) - General Correspondence
  - Letter to M. Fuson from Wallace Westfeldt of NBC
  - Memo to Participants in UPUSA Conference on the Southeast from John H. Marion
  - Memo: Executive Committee Meeting with Minutes
  - Newsletter from M. Fuson 10/64 Letter to Board Members from M. Fuson Notes-handwritten
  - Memo to Members of NCRC from M. Fuson
  - Notice of Noon Meeting
  - Memo to Members of NCRC from M. Fuson
  - President's Report by Marian Fuson, 10/63-5/65
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Community Relations Council (NCRC) - General Correspondence - James Laney, 1968 July-December
  - Memo to Members of Executive Committee with Agenda
  - Letter to Church Women United from James Laney
  - Letter from James Laney, President NCRC to Mayor Beverly Briley, with response
  - Letter from James Laney, President NCRC to Dan May, Chair, Metro Action Commission
  - Letter to James Laney from Carleen Waller 9/68 Letter to James Laney from Richard H. Bauer
  - Letter to James Laney from Loretta Y. Tucker, Secretary to John Dean
  - Minutes of Meeting of Executive Committee
  - Memo to All Ministers, Nashville Area from James E. Mock
  - Report of the Treasurer, 5/20/68-10/3/68
  - Memo to Board Members Re: Resolution
  - Notes from the Desk of James Laney
  - Handwritten Notes
  - Minutes of Metro Board of Education
  - Letter to Friend form T. Scott Fillebrown of Nashville Religious Society of Friends
  - Memo to Members of NCRC Re: Resolution presented to Metro Board of Education
  - Recommendation to Metro Board of Education from James Laney
  - Letter to James Laney from C. R. Dorrier of Metro Board of Education
  - List of Officers of Executive Committees of NCRC
  - List of Participants at Meeting
  - Notes on Meeting
  - Notice of Sadie Wilson Tillman Lectures at Martin College
  - Memo to Forum Participants from James Laney
  - Meeting Notice: Annual Meeting, Open Forum, Membership Meeting
  - Letter to Mr. Bridges from James Laney
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Community Relations Council (NCRC) - Board of Directors Minutes, with Ordinances for Commissions on Human Rights
  - Memo to Board Members from T. A. Smedley Re: Organizational Meeting
  - Memo to Board of Directors from T. A. Smedley Re: Policy Committee Report
  - Minutes of Board
  - Job Mobilization Support Sheet
  - CEPA Membership Form
  - Model City Code of Fair Practices
  - Henderson Ordinance for the Commission on Human Rights Hopkinsville Ordinance Establishing a Commission on Human Rights Middlesboro, KY Ordinance Establishing a Commission on Human Rights Louisville Ordinance Establishing A Commission on Human Rights Reports of Nominating Committee-NCRC
  - Hopkinsville Ordinance Establishing a Commission on Human Rights
  - Middlesboro, KY Ordinance Establishing a Commission on Human Rights
  - Louisville Ordinance Establishing A Commission on Human Rights
  - Reports of Nominating Committee
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Community Relations Council (NCRC) - Board of Directors Minutes
  - Memo
  - Minutes of Executive Committee
  - Letter to Mayor Beverly Briley
  - Minutes of Board Meeting
  - Minutes of Board Meeting
  - Report of Nominating Committee
  - Meeting Agenda
  - Minutes of Board Meeting
  - Minutes of Meeting
  - Letter to Board Members from Lou Silberman
  - Minutes of Board Meeting
  - Memo to Board from Lou Silberman
  - Invitation to Annual Dinner Meeting of NCLC
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Student Non-Violent Movement - General Correspondence
  - Letter to Madison Sarratt, Chair of Mayor's Committee on Human Relations from Nashville Friends Meeting
  - Letter to Baptist Student Movement from Lowell Fewster, BSM President
  - Letter to Freedom Fighter from NSNVM Central Committee
  - Letter to the Community from James Bevel
  - Letter to Citizens of Nashville
  - Letter from NSNVM Central Committee 1962 Letter to Nashville Community Re: Unfair and Immoral Discrimination and Segregation
  - Letter from Diane Nash Bevel to Organizations working for Civil Rights
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Student Non-Violent Movement - Correspondence Re: 2/60 Sit-Ins
  - List of M. and N. Fuson's Tapes
  - Memo to Bernard Lafayette and Joan Bahner from N. Fuson Re: Fisk Students arrested in 2/60 Sit-ins
  - Handwritten list of students not arrested Fisk Forums
  - Possible Sit-in Participants from Fisk University
- Organizations and Community Activities - Nashville Student Non-Violent Movement -Voice of the Movement volumes
- Organizations and Community Activities - Tennessee Council on Human Relations (TCHC) - Correspondence and Minutes of Meetings
  - Minutes of Annual Membership Meeting
  - Letter to Mayor Beverly Briley from Avon Williams
  - Brochure to Join TCHC
  - Proposed Budget
  - Program of 8th Annual Meeting of TCHC
  - Letter to Friend from John E. Hill
  - Letter to Member of TCHC from Baxton Bryant
  - Letter to Council Member from T. A. Smedley
  - Letter Announcing Workshop from Baxton Bryant
- Organizations and Community Activities - Tennessee Council on Human Relations (TCHC) - Newsletters and Public Events Notices
  - Newsletter
  - Registration for Annual Meeting
  - Press Release: "African Students Arrested in Nashville" 3-5/65 Newsletter 3-4/66 Newsletter
  - Notice of Workshop: "Where is Nashville in Civil Liberties?"
  - Report of Workshop
- Organizations and Community Activities - Philadelphia Yearly Meetings of the Religious Society of Friends
  - Proposed Statement on Race Relations
  - Letter to Fusons from James Coan of the Social Order Committee Notes: Don't Forget
- Organizations and Community Activities - Poor People's Campaign American Friends Service Committee
  - Written Program of Information on the Poor People's Campaign
  - Newsletter from A Quaker Action Corps
  - Newsletter from A Quaker Action Group
  - Newsletter from A Quaker Action Group
  - Newlsetter: "The Phoenix Wind-Up"
  - Poor People's Campaign Bulleting: "New Timetable" Map to March Site at Tennessee State Fair Grounds
  - Letter to Friend from Wilton E. Hartzler of American Friends Service Committee